Jujutsu Kaisen Let's go.
BIRDS CHIRP
Let's go.
I don't know.
Oh, God.
I'm not sure what you're doing.
Thank
you
so
much for watching.
So, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I can't change.
Well here we go.
I'm not loving it.
You're not loving it.
Love me, love me, love you.
The sound of this song Loving,
love me, I'm so Browning.
Show me, turn me.
This is the sound of this song, I
feel like it's all right. What's up?
No, no, no, no.
I can't change your mind,
So, tell me, is Mai dead?
It's the clan head you
should be concerned about,
and Maki's the one who's
nearly dead, not Mai.
Is that so?
Well, I'm glad to hear it.
Maki's a real beauty, but she's no good.
She can't support a man.
Any woman who can't walk
humbly behind her man
deserves to be stabbed
in the back and killed.
Now, Mai's a great woman in that regard.
She has the same face and
the same great rack as Maki.
She may put on a brave face, but she
understands her place as a woman.
You're late.
Where were you, and what
have you been doing?
Your father's in critical condition.
Sorry about that.
But what difference does
it make if I'm here or not?
Either way, I'm going to be the
next head of the Zenin clan.
All my older brothers are
a bunch of knuckleheads.
And Uncle, you're his little brother,
but you haven't got what it takes.
And your daughters are
out of the question.
And Jinichi, well...
You don't look the part.
If you had Toji's looks, it
would be a different story.
My father's dying, cut
me some slack, would you?
We're all a little on edge.
I see everyone's finally here.
I've been informed that Naobito
Zenin, head of the Zenin clan,
has unfortunately taken his last breath.
I am Furudate.
I was entrusted by Naobito to read his
will to you, his chosen family members,
upon his passing.
Ogi Zenin, Jinichi Zenin, and Naoya Zenin.
Since you are all gathered here today,
I shall begin the reading immediately.
Unless, of course, any of you
have an objection to my doing so.
First item, Naoya Zenin shall be
made the 27th head of the Zenin Clan.
Second item,
Naoya shall inherit all assets and
cursed tools that are currently
stored in either Jujutsu High or
the Zenin Clan's Forbidden Vaults.
In addition to that,
Naoya shall require
agreement from either Ogi or
Jinichi Zenin before
making use of any contents.
I guess that's fine.
However, in the event that
Satoru Gojo dies before I do,
or otherwise loses the use
of his mental faculties,
then the covenant with Toji
Fushiguro shall be fulfilled.
Megumi Fushiguro will be
welcomed into the Zenin clan,
and that same person will become the new
head of the Zenin clan
and inherit its assets.
Huh what the hell those guys have
no balls they think some unknown
brat is ahead would be better than
me so they ain't doing jack about it
where's megumi and what is he doing
now i don't know much only that he's
on a mission to find yuji itadori
somewhere in the tokyo and who's that
he is the vessel of sukuna then go
tell the big shots that naoya zenin is
going to kill sukuna's vessel and since
megumi is with sukuna's vessel i'll
kill them both together tokyo is in
pandemonium right now people can die
any time for any reason there once i
kill him the rest will work itself out
the zenin clan belongs to me
itadori
itadori itadori What will you be doing?
Yuji, how are your injuries?
Fine, except for where I took that
black flash, but I'm healing fast.
It's probably because of Sukuna.
I can feel how his power
has grown stronger.
Yuji, don't worry about me.
Go back to Jujutsu High.
I'd like to retrieve the
remains of Choso and the others.
I'm not worried.
It's not an issue of me
wanting to return or not.
Sukuna's plotting something
that uses Fushiguro.
Plus, I've killed so many people.
How are you going to feel when someone you
save goes on to kill someone else later?
I don't think I can stay
with the others anymore.
How do you feel, Choso?
You know I killed your
little brothers, too.
It's fine.
That was an accident.
Esau and Kechizu would have done the
same if they were in my position.
Forgiving you or not doesn't matter.
That's what it means to be siblings.
Let's go.
We need to reduce the
number of cursed spirits.
Oh, my God.
Huh?
Let's go.
I got him.
How terrifying.
I already sensed he was
powerful when he fought.
Now he's added subtlety to it.
He is unfaltering control
of his cursed energy.
An exceptional physical strength.
He's like a war god.
Crazy that he wasn't
in top shape until now.
You're very impressive, little brother.
Do you have to keep saying that?
As often as it takes.
Remember, he should have been there.
Your father should have also had stitches.
With his forehead, too.
Don't tell me Megumi's not here.
Am I the first to arrive?
How's that even possible?
He's way too slow.
Who's this guy?
Why is he looking for Fushiguro?
What are you doing out here anyway?
You don't exactly blend in.
Planning an escape? Escape?
What, you don't know?
You've been sentenced to death.
After all, you no longer
have Satoru's protection.
There are lots of sorcerers who have
been saved due to Gojo's influence,
pride, and wimps.
My business is with Megumi.
So to be blunt, I couldn't
care less if you live or die.
Then again,
I don't want you running
around willy-nilly,
so I'm going to break your legs for now.
What do you want Fushiguro for?
I need him to die.
But it'd be great if he could
sign some papers before he goes.
By the way, I heard he's looking for you.
He's certainly faster than us
but something is off probably
his technique you're doing
better than i expected i honestly
underestimated you i know the
vessel's got stuff going on but what's
that thing beside him i guess
i'll crank up the speed a bit more
am i feeling gojo
no it's even creepier three of
you i thought you'd be alone
who is that whoever he is it's bad
What are your relationships to Itadori?
So he's also here to execute Yuji.
Hold up, pal.
I'm on your side.
Your name is Okotsu, right?
Okotsu?
The second year Fushiguro talked about.
A special great sorcerer.
Just like Gojo.
And you are?
I'm Naoya Zenin, you know, Maki's cousin.
And I'm here to kill
Itadori, just like you are.
Yuji, we have to run.
So relax.
I'll stay out of your way.
The blonde one's fast
with some kind of trick.
We need to avoid getting into
a chase. I'll stall. Now go.
Will you be okay?
And in return for staying out of
your way after you kill Itadori,
maybe you could hold off
a bit before reporting it.
I want to use him as bait for
someone else. I'll be fine.
You're the one they've
come here for, not me.
Okotsu.
Just worry about getting away from him.
He seems like the same type as Gojo.
You'll die if you fight him.
I should have kept quiet about Megumi.
Me and my big mouth.
My plan keeps Yuji from
fighting another human.
And prevents him from
feeling guilty toward me.
He's such a handful.
Meet up at yesterday's spot, Yuji.
Sounds fine.
I'll leave that one to you then. Now!
He's fast!
And with that sword drawn, too!
He's pretty quick.
I'd planned to crush him
when he broke into a run.
I was trying to block Akutsu's
path, but you read my move.
I was watching you earlier.
That's blood manipulation, right?
Only I can't figure out why you can do it.
Still, it's not that scary
aside from piercing blood.
And producing piercing
blood takes convergence.
There's a long build-up.
I don't think there's
anything left to say.
It's checkmate.
You're going to die.
You're the one who will die.
Did you think you could go after my little
brother and then leave this place alive?
I'm sure I was able to cut him.
He's like Maki.
Surprised?
I don't seem like the power type, do I?
Even with uproar power, he has an
insane amount of Cursed Energy.
I actually am on the weaker side.
He's enhancing himself with Cursed
Energy to cover for his lack of strength.
Everyone does that to some
degree, but when he does it,
it's the exact opposite of me.
Have you noticed?
I have more Cursed Energy
than your teacher, Gojo.
However, Gojo has his six eyes.
So he wastes practically no energy at all.
When he activates his techniques.
He's the best there is when
it comes to performance.
Unlike your teacher, I can
run out of cursed energy.
Enough chit-chat.
It's the better the sorcerer.
the harder it is to read the
flow of their cursed energy.
Yours will be hard to read as well.
That's because the better the sorcerer,
the more precise their cursed energy.
That means you can't predict their
attack until the last second.
But with this guy, there's
cursed energy constantly rising?
from his entire body, even his sword.
It's not even a question
of reading his moves.
He can land decisive flows
with all his attacks,
and he can reduce all
damage to the bare minimum.
You take it from here.
Sorry, Okotsu, but I can't
afford to die just yet.
There are some types who centered their
training around the use of a weapon.
But you don't want to become
dependent on a cursed tool
and then neglect your
manipulation of cursed energy.
So Slaughter Demon is
just an emergency measure.
You've never taught me this!
You're putting too much
focus into the blade.
It broke?
Of course it did.
He's one of Gojo's students.
I guess you're not going down easily.
The wound's deep, but none
of my organs are falling out.
And now we're both unarmed. I can win!
We're playing, Rika. That's all.
Rika?
What is this thing?
A Shikigami?
Where did it come from?
Hold him still.
I can't move!
So strong!
I'm sorry,
Itadori.
I'll see
you
next time.
Older brothers less competent than
younger brothers serve no purpose.
I can't understand how you
never loved your brothers.
Please report Itadori's death.
That's when all the distortion started.
Don't look down on me.
Start by saving me.
This is Checkmate.
Sumiki has been drawn into this game too.